unitemps.com 2015-09-23

# Unitemps - Privacy policy

**Privacy Policy**  
Unitemps is committed to ensuring your privacy is protected. When signing up for a Unitemps account, we collect your personal data as per the registration form. We will not contact you other than to send you the bulletins you have subscribed for or internal news about our services for jobseekers, or offers from our partner companies and we will not distribute any of the details you provide to a third party. We have put in place suitable security procedures to safeguard your information.

 **Cookies**  
The Unitemps Website uses cookies to provide enhanced functionality and to gather information about how the site is being used to help us continually improve the user experience. For more details about what cookies are, the cookies that we use and how to disable them, please see our Cookie Policy

 **Right to Access Your Personal Information**  
As an individual, the Data Protection Act 1998 gives you a right to access information we hold about you. You can obtain access to your personal information held by us by making a Subject Access Request. You are asked to complete a [DP1 Form](http://www2.warwick.ac.uk/services/legalservices/freedomofinformation/sar/dp1_form.doc), which should then be submitted by email to [infocompliance@warwick.ac.uk](mailto:infocompliance@warwick.ac.uk) or mail it to:

Administrative Officer (Compliance)  
Deputy Registrar's Office  
University House   
University of Warwick  
Coventry  
CV4 8UW

In addition you will need to send a £10 fee, together with copies of two forms of ID (passport, driving licence, staff/student badge etc). This fee is payable by cheque (made payable to the ‘University of Warwick’), cash, or debit/credit card.

Further information on Subject Access Requests can be found here:  
<http://www2.warwick.ac.uk/services/legalservices/freedomofinformation/sar/>
